I'm hungry again!
(Howard:)It's like the world's
fattest cuckoo clock.
(Bernadette:)You know, you're always talking
about having a baby someday.
-This is exactly what it'll be like.
-No, it's not.
(Bernadette:)Come on. The constant fussing,
eating, pooping, burping, drooling.
(Bernadette:)We're even waiting for the day
when she can finally walk on her own.
(Howard:)Maybe you're right.
(Howard:)Anything she finds on the floor
goes right in her mouth.
(Bernadette:)I'm just telling you now,
if we do have kids,
(Bernadette:)don't expect me to do all the work.
(Howard:)Hey, I'm a very paternal person.
(Howard:)I'd be excellent
at taking care of a baby.
l'm still hungry!
I'm coming, you big baby!